<resources>
    <!--Setting's-->
    <!--Адрес основного сервера-->
    <string name="swim_api_server_address" translatable="false">192.168.31.181:8080</string>


    <!--All-->
    <string name="app_name">SwimBySvyter</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--hint's-->
    <string name="hint_login">Login</string>
    <string name="hint_pass">Password</string>
    <string name="hint_email" translatable="false">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_pass_repeat">Repeat password</string>


    <!--Page's-->
    <string name="menu_home">Trainings</string>
    <string name="menu_favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="menu_theory">Theory</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="menu_completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="menu_exit">Exit</string>

    <!--Profile-->
    <string name="profile_age">Age</string>
    <string name="profile_count_train_one_week">The number of training for 1 week</string>
    <string name="profile_count_week">Count week</string>
    <string name="profile_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="profile_length_pool">Length pool</string>
    <string name="profile_time_train">Training time</string>
    <string name="profile_complexity">Complexity</string>
    <string name="profile_edit_btn">Edit</string>
    <!--DialogProfile-->
    <string name="save">Save</string>

    <!--Detail-->
    <string name="inv_header">Inventories</string>
    <string name="completed">Completed</string>

    <!--Questioner-->
    <string name="auth_comment">Stop putting it off for later, individual training is already waiting for you!</string>


    <!--Login-->
    <string name="forget_pass">Forget password?</string>
    <string name="log_in">Log In</string>
    <string name="reg_account_txt">Don\'t have account?</string>
    <string name="sing_up">Sing Up</string>

    <!--Registration-->
    <string name="reg_confidentiality">I agree with the conditions of service and the confidentiality policy</string>
    <string name="reg_btn">Create account</string>
    <string name="reg_have_account">Do you have account?</string>
    <string name="sing_in">Sing In</string>

    <!--Theory-->
    <string name="swim_style_front_crawl">
1. Freestyle (Front Crawl)\n
&#10;Features: The fastest swimming style, used in most competitions. Known for high efficiency and streamlining.\n
&#10;Technique:\n
&#10;Arms alternate in circular strokes forward, entering the water in front of the shoulder. After catching the water, the arm pulls under the body and recovers above the surface.\n
&#10;Legs perform quick and strong flutter kicks from the hips, with heels slightly breaking the surface.\n
&#10;Breathing — turn your head to the side during the arm recovery phase; avoid lifting it too high.\n
&#10;Tip:\n
&#10;- Keep your body elongated and straight.\n
&#10;- Use minimal effort for maximum glide.\n
&#10;- Coordinate arms, legs, and breathing smoothly.\n
</string>

    <string name="swim_style_brass">
&#10;&#10;2. Breaststroke\n\n
&#10;Features: The slowest but most stable stroke. Great for long-distance swimming and beginners learning technique.\n
&#10;Technique:\n
&#10;Arms move simultaneously forward, then sweep outwards and back to the chest.\n
&#10;Legs perform a frog kick — heels drawn to the hips, then pushed out and together.\n
&#10;Breathing — during the head lift at the start of the arm pull.\n
&#10;Tip:\n
&#10;- Maintain perfect synchronization of arm and leg movements.\n
&#10;- Pause briefly in a fully extended glide after each cycle.\n
&#10;- Focus on clean technique over speed.\n
    </string>

    <string name="swim_style_butterfly">
&#10;&#10;3. Butterfly\n\n
&#10;Features: The most physically demanding style. Requires strength and flexibility, especially in the back and core.\n
&#10;Technique:\n
&#10;Arms move together in a wide pull: enter the water in front of the head, catch and push down and back.\n
&#10;Legs perform dolphin kicks — a fluid wave motion from the chest to the feet. Two kicks per arm cycle.\n
&#10;Breathing — raise your head after the main arm pull when the shoulders exit the water.\n
&#10;Tip:\n
&#10;- Drive the motion with your torso, not just the legs.\n
&#10;- Breathe rhythmically, ideally every cycle.\n
&#10;- Train back, shoulder, and core muscles outside the water as well.\n

    </string>

    <string name="swim_style_backstroke">
&#10;&#10;4. Backstroke\n\n
&#10;Features: The only style swum on the back. Allows for free breathing but requires good navigation.\n
&#10;Technique:\n
&#10;Arms alternate, entering the water above the head and pulling along the side of the body to the hip.\n
&#10;Legs perform flutter kicks, similar to freestyle. Kicks should be steady and come from the hips.\n
&#10;Breathing — unrestricted, as the face remains above the water.\n
&#10;Tip:\n
&#10;- Look straight up or slightly back; avoid lifting your chin.\n
&#10;- Keep your arms close to the head during recovery.\n
&#10;- Use visual cues (ceiling or shore) to stay oriented.\n
    </string>

</resources>